Here's the process I want you to follow.
.تلك هي العملية التي أريد منكم اتباعها
It has several steps.
.وهي تتضمن العديد من الخطوات
The first is to take the name of your algorithm and
الأولى هي أخذ اسم الخوارزمية
head on to Google to do some research.
،والبحث عنه على موقع Google
Get a general understanding of what the algorithm does.
.ومن ثم الحصول على فهم عام عما تفعله هذه الخوارزمية
If you can explain the algorithm to a friend, for example, then you
إذا أمكنكم شرح الخوارزمية إلى صديق، على سبيل المثال، فذاك يعني أنكم
probably understand it well enough that you're ready to move on the next step.
.فهمتموها جيدًا وأنكم جاهزون للانتقال إلى الخطوة التالية
Then what I suggest you do is find the sklearn documentation for
بعد ذلك، ما أقترح عليكم فعله هو البحث عن وثائق Sklearn الخاصة بهذه
this algorithm, exactly the way we've been doing all throughout this course.
.الخوارزمية، وهي الطريقة المتبعة طوال هذه الدورة التدريبية
Remember that the sklearn documentation also usually has examples.
.تذكروا أن وثائق Sklearn عادة ما يتوفر بها أمثلة
This would be a huge help for
وسيساعدكم هذا الأمر في
you in the next step, step number three, which is to deploy the algorithm.
.الخطوة التالية - رقم ثلاثة - والتي تتمثل في نشر الخوارزمية
Get your hands dirty.
.فليشارك كل منكم عمليًا في هذا الأمر
Try to get it running at least.
.حاولوا تشغيل الخوارزمية على الأقل
That's, of course, the first thing that you need before you can go on to
وهذا بالطبع الشيء الأول الذي تحتاجون إليه قبل الانتقال إلى
step number four, which is using it to make some predictions about the test set.
.الخطوة الرابعة، والمتمثلة في استخدام الخوارزمية لإجراء تنبؤات حول مجموعة الاختبار
And then, of course, you use those predictions to evaluate it.
.وستستخدمون بالطبع تلك التنبؤات لتقييمها
What's the accuracy on the test set?
ما هي دقة مجموعة الاختبار؟
I've given you set of starter code that has all the training and
قد أعطيتكم مجموعة من تعليمة بادئ التشغيل البرمجية التي بها
testing data ready to go.
.كل بيانات التدريب والاختبار الجاهزة للاستخدام
There's also a function in there that allows you to plot it, so
وثمة دالة أخرى هنا تتيح لكم رسمها، لذا
you can visualize the decision boundary,
،يمكنكم عرض حد القرار
which is always something that's really nice to do.
.والذي دائمًا ما يكون شيئًا رائعًا حقًا لفعله
By the time you've completed this process, you will be a real machine learning
وبمرور الوقت، تكونون قد أكملتم هذه العملية، وأصبحتم خبراء
expert in the sense that maybe you don't know everything yet.
.في التعلم الآلي لكن هناك أشياء عليكم تعلمها في المستقبل
The very few machine learning experts would say they know everything.
.فهناك القليل من خبراء التعلم الآلي يمكنهم القول عن أنفسهم إنهم يعرفون كل شيء
The thing that separates the good ones from the great ones
والشيء الذي يفصل بين الأشخاص الجيدين والخبراء عادة
is very often that they're able to go out and learn something new,
،ما يتمثل في قدرتهم على اكتشاف وتعلم أشياء جديدة
and this is your chance to do that.
.وهذه هي فرصتكم للقيام بذلك